http://www.outdooradventurestore.ie/terms-conditions

Search
Account
Home GiveawayAbout UsContact UsTerms and ConditionsPrivacy StatementOpening HoursDelivery & ReturnsBlogCorporate Services & SalesCareersCart
MenuMens Clothing Trekking Trousers & ShortsWaterproof JacketsWaterproof OvertrousersInsulated JacketsGore-TexSoftshellsFleecesShirts & T-ShirtsBase LayersHats, Gloves & AccessoriesRainwear AccessoriesFootwear Mountain Hiking BootsHillwalking BootsWalking ShoesHiking SocksFootwear AccessoriesKids RainwearFootwearPetsWomens Clothing Trekking Trousers & ShortsWaterproof JacketsWaterproof OvertrousersInsulated JacketsGore-TexSoftshellsFleecesShirts & T-ShirtsBase LayersHats, Gloves & AccessoriesRainwear AccessoriesFootwear Mountain Hiking BootsHillwalking BootsWalking ShoesHiking SocksFootwear AccessoriesKids RainwearFootwearPetsEquipment Tents Trekking TentsAdventure TentsFamily & Airbeam TentsInflatable TentsAll TentsPegs, Poles & AccessoriesGroup TentageFootprints & CarpetsSleeping All Sleeping BagsAbove 0°C-0°C-5°CFamily CampingMats, Matresses & BedsLiners & AccessoriesRucksacks Single-Day Hiking (0-35L)Multi-Day Hiking (36-50L)Trekking (50-70L)Expedition Packs (70+L)Lifestyle BackpacksDuffel BagsChild CarriersTravel & LuggageHydration PacksRucksack AccessoriesCamping Hand TorchesHead TorchesLanternsFurnitureCooler Boxes & JerrycansPower SuppliesHeatersCooking & Eating Stoves & GasTrangiaPots, Pans & UtensilsInstant MealsHydration BottlesFlasksBladdersHydration AccessoriesHiking & Outdoors CompassesMapsWalking & Trekking PolesMountain SurvivalFirst Aid KitsRepair KitsKnives Multi-ToolsKnivesActivities Camping TentsPegs, Poles & AccessoriesSleeping BagsMats, Matresses & BedsLiners & AccessoriesHand TorchesHead TorchesLanternsFurnitureHiking DaysacksRucksacksRucksack AccessoriesBottlesBladdersFlasksCompassesMapsWalking & Trekking PolesFirst Aid KitsMountain SurvivalTravel TowelsWash GearMosquito NetsMosquito RepellentsWater PurificationSecurityAccessoriesSunglassesRock-Climbing HelmetsAccessories , BooksBelays , Ascenders , DescendersWatersports WetsuitsWatersports AccessoriesVouchersBrands A-G 1000 MileAdventure Safety IrelandBerghausBolleBridgedaleBuffCampingazColemanCébéCraghoppersDare2bDexshellEastpakEastWest MappingFirepotForce10GoSystemGrangersG-L Helly HansenHi-TecKelly KettleLeathermanLed LenserLekiLifeSystemsLifeVentureLowe AlpineLittleLifeMaier SportsMerrellMountain EquipmentMSRNikwaxO-T Ordnance Survey IrelandOspreyPacSafePetzlPlatypusRock N RiverSeal LineSealskinzSiggSilvaSnugpakSpraywayStormsureSummitT-Z Target DryThermarestTilley HatsTrangiaTrekMatesTrespassTyphoonVangoVictorinox Swiss ArmyWayfayrerZamberlanDealsClearanceBlogEURGBPFree Delivery over €40Free Returns PolicyCall us: 01-2764426Close menuEURGBPFree Delivery over €40Free Returns PolicyCall us: 01-2764426Terms & Conditions 1. Introduction1.1 The website is owned and operated by the Outdoor Adventure Store (referred to as "we", "us" or "our"), which shall also include our third party suppliers and any other affiliates involved in the maintenance and running of this site.1.2 The Outdoor Adventure Store offers this website, including all information, features services available from this site to you, the user based on your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here. If you are not in agreement with these terms and conditions, then you should refrain from using this website and its services.1.3 These Terms and Conditions apply to all users of this website, including without limitation users who are browsers, customers, merchants, and/ or contributors of content. By visiting or purchasing something from our site, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”).1.4 By agreeing to these Terms and conditions you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your place of residence, or that you have been given the consent to use, view and transact on this site.1.5 Those who visit the Site from locations outside of the Republic of Ireland do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with all Irish applicable laws. If the use of the site or any of the information is in contradiction with your local jurisdiction(s), you must refrain from the use of this site. 2. Copyright & Liability2.1 All content and materials published on the site are presented to you solely for your private, personal and non-commercial use. All contents of the site are protected by national and international intellectual property laws, and/or is owned by The Outdoor Adventure Store or its suppliers, therefore, the copying or imitation of these goods, brands and trademarks are prohibited. 3. Online materials3.1 Where content on our website is supplied by a third party that is not affiliated with us, you are aware that The Outdoor Adventure Store does not control or monitor this content. As far as we are aware this content is of good nature, however, we are not liable for any harm or damages caused as a result of your relationship with a third party website. You are responsible for the risk associated with the use of this site and your interpretation of the information displayed. 4. Prohibitions4.1 In addition to any other prohibitions set within these terms and conditions you are also prohibited from using this site for any unlawful purposes whether it be yourself or the solicitation of others to do so. You are also prohibited from engaging in any illegal activities whilst on our site. You must refrain from using our products for any illegal or unauthorized purposes.4.2 You are also prohibited from uploading or transmitting viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the service or of any third party related website. In addition, you are prohibited from collecting or tracking the personal information of others and/or engaging in the spamming, hacking or infecting of any aspect of our services. 5. Site Availability5.1 Even though The Outdoor Adventure Store will use its best endeavours to provide you with an error-free service this cannot be guaranteed. In some cases the continuous operation of our site may experience some rare unexpected interruptions, therefore we are not liable for its unavailability. 6. General6.1 We reserve the right to update, change or replace any part of these terms by posting updates and/or changes to our website. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for changes as this page will be updated with new services, features or tools.6.2 The Outdoor Adventure Store reserve the right to change, replace or remove any part of these TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE with no notice required. The site will then be governed by the amended terms when they are made public. Therefore it is your responsibility to check the terms and conditions on the site regularly. You will find the latest version on this web page.6.3 Prices for our products are subject to change without notice. We reserve the right at any time to modify the pricing or the range of products we offer. We have the right to discontinue any part of our service or any of our products at any time. We shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price change, suspension or discontinuance of the service. 7. Personal information7.1 Your submission of personal information through the store is governed by our Privacy Policy. Our E-commerce solution is provided to you by Payzone through their online payment gateway allowing you to purchase our products and services online. Your credit and debit card details submitted when making a payment are hosted through Payzone who are in compliance with PCI: DSS, therefore these details will be kept encrypted and private and will not be given to any third party or affiliates.7.2 We reserve the right to refuse any order you place with us if we believe the order to be suspicious or lacking information. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order including orders placed with the same credit card or orders using the same billing and/or shipping address. In order to prevent these events from occurring you agree to provide current, complete and accurate purchase and account information for all purchases made at our online store.TrustpilotNewsletter SignupOffers & NewsSecure Payments by ShopMensWomensEquipmentActivitiesVouchersBrandsDealsClearanceHelpHomeAbout UsContact UsTerms and ConditionsPrivacy StatementOpening HoursDelivery & ReturnsBlogCorporate Services & SalesCareersContactOutdoor Adventure Store,Unit 5 Bray South Business ParkKillarney Road, Bray,Co. WicklowView Map01-2764426online@oas.ieAboutIn addition to outdoor adventures, we believe passionately in travel, naps, good food, great friends, long talks, broadened horizons + a spirit of adventure.TrustpilotTerms & ConditionsPrivacy Statement © Outdoor Adventure Store 2020Successfully added to basketGo To CheckoutContinue ShoppingWe use necessary cookies to make this site work, we also use optional analytics cookies to enhance user experience - but these are disabled by default See our Cookie PolicyAccept AllReject AllSettings
